晚饭想不想换个花样
You feel like trying something new for dinner?
德墨菜  德州式墨西哥菜
美国的德克萨斯州和墨西哥接壤
要不试试印度菜或者德墨菜
Maybe Indian, Tex-Mex?
你有没有好奇过  如果人类是从蜥蜴
You ever wonder how humans would be different
而不是哺乳动物进化而来  会有啥区别
if they evolved from lizards instead of mammals?
好吧  你说吧
Okay, let's talk about that.
你也知道  蜥蜴这种冷血动物
As you know, lizards-- cold-blooded animals--
缺乏感知温度的能力
lack the ability to sense temperature.
但它们确实在低温环境下行动更迟缓
But they do move more sluggishly when it's cold.
所以呢  蜥蜴天气预报员会这么说话
So, lizard weathermen would say things like,
"带上件毛衣  外面好慢[冷]"
"Bring a sweater, it's slow outside."
我爱死自己的犀利头脑了
I love my mind.
我们也是
We all do.
快说  晚饭吃啥
Now, how about dinner?
大多数蜥蜴吃动物性食物  主要是各种昆虫
体型较大的蜥蜴会以其他蜥蜴为食物
我猜我们会享受吃昆虫和小蜥蜴的盛宴
Oh, I would assume we'd enjoy insects or smaller lizards.
我们也可以扯掉对方的尾巴然后烤着吃
We could also pull each other's tails off and grill them;
反正还能再长回来
they'll just grow back.
史波克先生  《星际迷航》中的大副先生
我的真人大小的卡纸板史波克先生到了
My life-size cardboard Mr. Spock is here!
我知道他不喜欢常人情感的瞬间流露
I know he wouldn't care for an outburst of human emotion,
可是  好棒哦  好棒哦  好棒哦
but, oh, goodie, oh, goodie, oh, goodie.
史波克中校请求拆封
Commander Spock requesting permission to be unfolded.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
允许拆封  中校
Permission granted, Commander.
这就是为什么越聪明的猴子
Which is why the more intelligent the monkey,
就越喜欢扔大便
the more feces they fling.
打断一下  艾米
Excuse me, Amy.
佩妮  你今天的晚饭有安排吗
Penny, do you have plans for dinner tonight?
怎么了  你们要去什么好地方吗
Why, you guys going somewhere?
不是  就咱俩单独吃
No, I mean just you and me.
像约会那样吗
You mean, like a date?
不是约会的那种约会
Not like a date, a date.
呃  好吧
Um... o-okay.
行啊
Sure.
天啊
Oh, no!
这不是我要的史波克
They sent the wrong Spock!
电视剧版《星际迷航》史波克的扮演者
生生不息  早日去死  扎克瑞・昆图
Live long and suck it, Zachary Quinto.
■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧原创翻译 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：MADD  Tina  海因里希  小蛮腰
后期：孤帆    时间轴：YY
■
校对：YY  MADD     总监：YY
生活大爆炸  第五季第十三集
太好了
This is so exciting.
要是莱纳德和佩妮复合了
If Leonard and Penny get back together,
我和霍华德就可以跟他们一起四人约会了
Howard and I can go on double dates with them.
你怎么从来不邀请谢尔顿和我参加四人约会呢
How come you never invite Sheldon and me on a double date?
你衣服试得怎么样了  佩妮
How's it going in there, Penny?!
稍等片刻
Just a sec.
是不是太隆重了
Too much?
-确实  -才没有
- Yes. - No.
好吧  再等一下
Okay, just hang on.
你受不了她那股天生的骚劲  对吧
You just can't handle her raw sexuality, can you?
你和莱纳德是什么时候分手的
When did you and Leonard break up?
差不多两年前吧
Uh, about two years ago.
你觉得他约你吃饭的原因是什么
Why do you think he asked you out again?
不知道
I don't know.
也许是他命不久矣
Maybe he's dying.
那该有多浪漫啊
That would be so romantic.
他命长着呢
He's not dying.
真可惜
Too bad.
如果是的话  她就可以把莱纳德推到在床
If he were, she could just throw him in bed
骑在他身上尽性  直到他心跳停止
and ride him right up until he flatlines.
这件怎么样
How about this?
-还行  -拜托
- Maybe. - Come on.
好吧  这件不行
Yeah, okay, no.
你觉得你今晚会和他上床吗
Do you think you'll sleep with him tonight?
绝对不会
Absolutely not.
我们就是吃个饭
Look, we're just gonna have dinner
然后再看情况吧
and, you know, see how it goes.
如果他病入膏肓了  你会和他上床吗
If he were dying, would you sleep with him?
什么
What?!
假设他身患绝症
Assuming he were dying of something
而这种病不会通过性行为传播
that couldn't be sexually transmitted.
比如脑袋上的箭伤
You know, like a spear wound to the head.
够了  他的命长着呢
Okay, he is not dying.
你怎么知道  你是医生吗
How do you know? Are you a doctor?
不过你可以这么幻想嘛
You can make-believe, though.
有时候霍华德和我会假装他出现了心律失常
Sometimes Howard and I pretend that his arrhythmia is acting up
而我是一个性感的心脏病医生
and I'm a sexy cardiologist.
最好玩的部分是  我的护理服务可是不收费的哟
And the naughty part is I'm not in his HMO network.
算了  我不打算搞得好得多大件事
Screw it. I'm not gonna make a big deal out of this.
就是吃个晚饭嘛
It's just dinner.
跟死人一起吃
With a dead man.
艾米  别说了
Amy, stop it.
天啊  我好紧张
Oh, God, I'm so nervous.
放松啦
Relax.
你知道莱纳德一直都很喜欢你
You know Leonard's always been crazy about you.
不会有事的
It's gonna be great.
我知道  可是我们好不容易才到了
I know, but we've finally gotten to a place
见面聊天都不尴尬的地步
where we can hang out without it being weird.
万一出了什么岔子呢  然后怎么办
And what if something goes wrong? Then what?
我猜只有谢尔顿和我
Guess it'll just be Sheldon and me
去陪霍华德和伯纳黛特一起四人约会了
going on a double date with Howard and Bernadette.
是啊  我们好期待
Sure, we'd love that.
快换衣服  我俩可就指望你俩今晚的表现了
Change your clothes; we got a lot riding on this.
我想修条路
I want to build a road,
wood亦指勃起的阴茎
但我需要硬木
but I need wood.
你俩谁有硬木吗
Do either of you fellows have wood?
我不知道你们在笑什么
I don't understand the laughter.
《卡坦岛》的目标
The object of Settlers of Catan
就是修建道路和房屋
is to build roads and settlements.
所以需要硬木
To do so requires wood.
sheep有时用来指代发生性关系的女人
我现在有绵羊  缺硬木
Now, I have sheep; I need wood.
谁能拿硬木换我的绵羊
Who has wood for my sheep?
我这身看着怎么样
Okay, how do I look?
我更想知道  你为什么要这么做
More to the point, why are you doing this?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你忘了佩妮当初怎么对你的吗
Did you forget what Penny did to you?
你花了两年的时间  还玷污了我妹妹
It took you two years and defiling my sister
才把你的愁云惨淡换成嬉皮笑脸
to turn that frown upside down.
我没有玷污你妹妹  我们只是交往过
I didn't defile your sister,we had a relationship.
Brown Sugar 多数形容漂亮性感的黑人女性
我以前听你叫她"靓妹黑妞"呢
I heard you call her Brown Sugar.
在我看来  这就是玷污
In my book, that's defilement.
想听听我的意见吗
You want to know my opinion?
天啊  想听得不得了
Oh, boy, do I!
是故意说反话吗
Sarcasm?
不是
No.
那好吧
All right, then.
你之所以对佩妮这种
The reason you're fixated on
秀外痴中的姑娘念念不忘
a good-natured simpleton like Penny is that
是因为她跟你的第一位爱慕对象截然相反
she's the exact opposite of your first romantic attachment:
也就是你害怕的天才母亲
your brilliant yet intimidating mother.
你怎么会有这种想法
Where on earth did you get that from?
她的书《越缺爱的小孩越贪心》里写的
It's in her book, Needy Baby, Greedy Baby.
那也不代表就是真的
That doesn't make it true.
莱纳德  那本书可是非虚构类的
It's called nonfiction for a reason, Leonard.
回见
See you later.
如果有人把她那本书拍成电影
If they ever make a movie version of that book,
你们知道该由谁来扮演莱纳德的妈妈吗
you know who should play Leonard's mother?
桑德拉・布洛克  好莱坞著名女影星  演过不少爱情片
桑德拉・布洛克
Sandra Bullock.
为什么
Why?
因为她每部作品都诠释得很好
Because she's great in everything.
我们玩到哪儿了
Now, where were we?
对了  你们谁有硬木吗
Oh, yes. Does anyone have any wood?
拜托
Oh, come on!
人家只是想要硬木而已
I just want wood.
有必要要搞得这么难[硬]啊
Why are you making it so hard?
有什么词可以形容
So, do they have a name for a first date
跟以前相好过的人第一次约会吗
with someone you used to go out with?
这个问题问得好
Oh, that's a good question.
"尴尬"怎么样
How about "awkward"?
-这词挺恰当的  -对吧
- Yeah, that sounds right. - Yeah?
要不我们假装这真的是第一次约会
Hey, how about if we pretend we're actually on a first date?
-看看结果怎么样  -好啊
- See how that goes. - Okay.
胖妮  跟我说说你吧
So, Polly, tell me about yourself.
我叫佩妮
It's Penny.
对不起  真尴尬
Oh, sorry, yeah. Awkward.
没事  我想想
Okay, uh, let's see.
我来自内布拉斯加  我还很小的时候
I'm from Nebraska, and ever since I was a little girl,
就梦想着能搬到洛杉矶  成为一名电影明星
I dreamed of moving to L.A. and becoming a movie star.
不过上了四年的表演课
Anyway, after four years of acting lessons
当了四年服务员之后
and waiting tables,
我出演了一个痔疮广告
I've done a hemorrhoid commercial
和一个保龄球球道上面扮演过安妮・弗兰克
and a production of Anne Frank above a bowling alley.
所以梦想真的能实现的
So, you know, dreams do come true.
该你了
Your turn.
我想想
Uh, let's see.
我是加州理工学院的实验物理学家
Uh, I am an experimental physicist at Cal-Tech,
大部分研究都跟高功率激光有关
most of my research is with high-powered lasers,
我最近刚拿到一大笔政府资助金
and, oh, I've just gotten a big government grant
看看能不能用于研究
to see if they can be used to knock out
击落来袭的弹道导弹
incoming ballistic missiles.
哇  那能实现吗
Wow. Can they?
废话  当然不行
Oh, God, no.
不过看在这么多钱的份上
The money's pretty good.
我还用那设备来发射自己的蝙蝠信号[蝙蝠侠中的求救信号]
And I used the equipment to make my own Bat-signal.
蝙蝠信号
Bat-signal?
怎么  你是所谓的宅男吗
What are you, some kind of nerd?
不是所谓的宅男  而是宅男之王
Not some kind of nerd, I'm the king of the nerds.
宅男之王是什么意思
What does that mean?
意思是谁要是惹恼我了
Uh, it means if anyone displeases me,
我就不帮他们装打印机
I don't help them set up their printer.
-你真幽默  -那就好
- You are so funny. - Good.
那我脱衣服的时候  你就想着这个优点好了
Remember that when I take my shirt off.
莱纳德  这样真好
Leonard, this is nice.
我很高兴我们能约会
I'm so glad we did this.
我也是
Me, too.
那你意下如何
So what do you think?
我们能复合吗
Are we gonna get back together?
不用这么快吧
Whoa. Not so fast.
对不起  我说错什么了吗
I'm sorry, what did I say?
莱纳德  你知道我对你的感觉永远不会变
Leonard, you know I will always have feelings for you.
-老天  -怎么了
- Oh, God. - What?
你说了"永远"
You said "always."
你对我的感觉永远不会变
You'll always have feelings for me.
有问题吗
So?
那听起来更像是在说
So, that sounds more like something you'd say
你不想和某人谈恋爱
if you didn't want a relationship with someone.
"我们不会有结果的"
"This isn't working out,"
"但我对你的感觉永远不会变"
"but I'll always have feelings for you."
"对不起  我跟你的好朋友睡了"
"I'm sorry I slept with your best friend,"
"但我对你的感觉永远不会变"
"but I'll always have feelings for you."
"是这样的  丽莎"
"Here's the thing, Lisa,
"我现在喜欢男的了  但我对你的感觉永远不会变"
I'm into dudes now, but I'll always have feelings for you."
那你会怎么说
How would you say it?
我对你的感觉不会变
I have feelings for you.
-这不是一样嘛  -不一样
- It's the same thing. - No, it's not.
加上"永远"只会适得其反
"Always" made it worse.
-你想太多了  -我没有
- You're overthinking this. - No, I'm not.
你有  你永远都是这样
Yes, you are. You always overthink things.
你看吧  一加"永远"就变味了
Th-There you go. "Always" made it worse.
瞧  我们一谈起来  就开始吵架
See, this is where everything goes wrong: when we talk.
谈恋爱当然要用"谈"的啦
Well, I don't know how you have a relationship without talking.
我以前还跟一个叫TJ的家伙在一起八个月
Hey, I went out with this guy TJ for eight months,
我们从来没谈过话
we never talked.
直到现在  我都不知道TJ代表啥
To this day, I don't even know what TJ stands for.
等等  你们要是不谈的话
Wait, if you guys didn't talk, what--
算了  这问题真二
Never mind, stupid question.
我现在有硬木了
And now that I have some wood,
我的殖民地要开始"崛起"了
I'm going to begin the erection of my settlement.
他肯定是故意这么说的
He's got to be doing this on purpose.
才八点半呢
Ooh, 8:30.
你跟佩妮是出去打酱油的吗
You and Penny decide to go out and paint the town beige?
某人都三十岁了  还跟妈妈同住一屋
You are 30 years old and you live with your mother.
看来约会不太顺利
I guess it didn't go well.
我们可不知道
We don't know that.
不能确定
Not to a certainty.
我们只知道莱纳德到家了
All we know is that Leonard is home.
现在呢
How about now?
证据还是不够
Again, not enough evidence.
我们只知道他被谋杀了
For all we know, he's being murdered.
现在  继续游戏
Now, back to our game.
你不是在"崛起"中吗
You were in the middle of an erection.
对哦  那"玩意儿"就在我手中
Oh, of course. It's right here in my hand.
她现在是想怎样
What does she want from me now?
怎么了
What's up?
别想太多
Do not overthink this.
-我不懂  -一切尽在不言中
- I don't understand. - Bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup.
好吧  但是之前不是...
Okay, but earlier it seemed like...
别说话
No talking.
做的时候也不说话吗  因为有时我会想提问耶
Even during? 'Cause sometimes I have questions.
挺不错
Well, that was fun.
是啊  除掉我脚抽筋的部分
Yeah, except for when I got the foot cramp.
但你还是挺住了
You hung in there, though.
牺牲小我  成全大我
There was a lot at stake.
你现在想做什么
So what do you want to do now?
我想去拿我的哮喘吸入器
Well, I want to go get my asthma inhaler,
但这样就太毁气氛了
but it might ruin the moment.
我还是不明白
Just, just help me out here.
为什么糟糕的约会能以滚床单收场
How does a miserable date end in sex?
我也不知道  这太复杂了
I don't know, it's complicated.
我很聪明的
Well, I'm a pretty smart guy,
而且现在血液主要在往大脑流动了
and right now my brain has dibs on the blood supply,
试试也无妨嘛
so give it a go.
好吧  只是...
Okay, it's just,
在餐厅里你说想
at the restaurant when you said
想跟我复合
you wanted us to be together again,
感觉太真实太突然了  我吓到了
it got very real very fast and I panicked.
为什么
Why?
你在怕什么
What are you afraid of?
要是我们真的和好了
Well, what if we do go out
但我又做了什么蠢事  又把你甩了怎么办
and I do something stupid and dump you again?
怎么就不是我甩你呢
What if I dump you?
得了  别闹
Come on, be serious.
那不然我们都不把这当成是谈恋爱
Well, how about if we don't think about this as a relationship?
就好比是一款新的软件
It could be more like a new version of software.
佩妮和莱纳德2.0升级版
Penny and Leonard 2.0.
我们可以先内测捉虫
We can test it internally, shake out the bugs,
等我们都觉得稳定了
and if we both feel it's solid,
到时再公之于众
then we'll roll it out to the public.
那我们先不告诉别人我们复合了
So we don't tell people we're back together?
是的
Exactly.
我们假装约会进展不顺利
We pretend like our date went badly.
这已经不用假装了
Well, we don't really have to pretend.
我们让他们以为我们决定只做朋友
And we let them think that we decided to just be friends
那样的话就没问题了
and that everything's cool.
好啊
Okay, great.
我刚想起来
Hey, I just remembered.
我还留着你的吸入器
I still got one of your inhalers.
不敢相信你还留着
I can't believe you kept this.
我本来想扔掉  但还是舍不得
Yeah, I was gonna throw it away, but I just couldn't.
你太贴心了
That is so sweet.
大概再过二十五到三十分钟  你就能知道
In 25 to 30 minutes I'm gonna show you
这对我的意义有多"重大"了
how much this means to me.
莱纳德
Leonard?
好啊
Yeah, hi, hi.
你好吗
How's it going?
没什么不好
Uh, can't complain.
不过还是谢谢
Thanks for asking.
你凌晨三点在外面做什么
Well, what were you doing out at 3:00 in the morning?
那你又在做什么
Well, uh, uh... what are you doing up?
我上厕所啊
I was using the bathroom.
我也是
Yeah, well, so was I.
真的吗
Really?
我怎么在里面没看到你
I didn't see you in there.
显然我看到你在用了
Obviously... when I saw that you were in ours,
所以我就出去用其它的了
I went and used another one.
上哪去用了
Where?
马路对面的加油站
The, the gas station across the street.
穿着睡衣去
In your pajamas?
是啊
Yes.
还没穿鞋去
Without shoes?
是啊
Yes.
大冬天三更半夜去
On a cold winter's night?
是啊
Yes.
不太可能啊
Seems unlikely.
你带你的哮喘吸入器了吗
Did you bring your asthma inhaler?
是的  我当然带了
Uh, uh, uh, yes, I did.
那貌似就可信了
Well, then, I guess it's plausible.
-等等  先生  -干嘛
- D-- hang on a second, mister. - What?
你用过加油站的厕所后
After you used the facilities at the gas station,
-买东西了吗  -什么
- did you make a purchase? - What?
这是国际惯例  你用了零售店的厕所
It's customary, when using the restroom
就要随便买点东西
at a retail establishment, to make a small purchase.
你买了吗
Did you?
没有
No.
给你两块钱
Here's two dollars.
去买点牛肉干
Go buy some beef jerky.
我不想吃牛肉干
I don't want beef jerky.
这不是你想不想的问题
It's not about you.
这关系到可怜的巴基斯坦移民
It's about a poor immigrant from Pakistan
在科罗拉多大道的
trying to make his way in America
雪佛龙公司上夜班
by working the graveyard shift
就为了在美国混口饭吃
at the Colorado Boulevard Chevron.
好吧
Fine.
还真是越缺爱的小孩越贪心啊
Needy Baby, Greedy Baby indeed.
莱纳德马上就来了
Leonard will be here in a moment.
他要重找一个停车位
He's looking for a different parking space.
为什么
Why?
我们旁边停着一辆车
We were next to a car
上面贴着一张贴纸  写着"聊聊我的孙子们"
with an "Ask me about my grandchildren." bumper sticker,
我担心如果走的时候遇到那辆车的车主
and I was afraid if we ran into them on the way out,
我就有义务就跟他聊
I'd be obligated to do so.
他跟佩妮的约会居然失败了  我好失望
I'm so disappointed it didn't work with him and Penny.
我也是
Me, too.
为了不伤害到他们
Out of deference to them,
咱们就别炫耀自家的完美恋情了
let's not flaunt our happy relationship.
你还真是体贴善良啊
You have a keen insight into the human heart,
艾米・费拉・福勒
Amy Farrah Fowler.
2000年美国总统选举中民主党的正副总统候选人
现在旁边那辆斯巴鲁上贴着一张写着"戈尔/利伯曼"的贴纸
We are next to a Suburu with a Gore/Lieberman bumper sticker.
我觉得他们不会想聊那个  所以我们安全了
Well, I doubt they'd want to talk about that, so we're fine.
你跟佩妮的约会搞砸了
I'm surprised to see you here
你居然还会来这吃饭
after it went so badly with Penny.
我们都是大人了
Well, hey, we're grown-ups.
买卖不成仁义在嘛
We can still be friends.
天啊  要是我跟霍华德分手了
Boy, I don't know if I could be friends with Howie
估计就做不成朋友了
if we broke up.
为什么
Why not?
我是个报复心很重的人
I'm a very vengeful person.
真的吗
Really?
而且我还能弄到改造成生化武器的天花
With access to weaponized smallpox.
伙计们  我先给你们上点水
Here you go, guys, let me get you going with some water.
你们要看菜单吗  还是已经想好要点什么了
You need menus or you know what you want?
莱纳德知道自己想要什么
Leonard knows what he wants,
不过看来从你这是捞不着了
but it looks like he's not gonna get it from you.
霍华德
Howard.
不  没事  伯纳黛特
No, that's okay, Bernadette.
有些人就是不适合在一起
Sometimes these things just don't work out.
没错  不过没关系
Yeah, it's all good.
我们  我们对彼此的感觉永远不会变
We-We'll always have feelings for each other.
还真是不错啊
Oh, that's nice.
看吧  她也知道"永远"的含义
See, she knew what "always" meant.
你就是得理不饶人是吧
Wow, you're like a dog with a bone, aren't you?
我只是想证明我的观点而已
I'm just making a point.
你不知道该何时放手的观点吗
Is the point that you don't know when to let something go?
够了  够了
People, people,
拜托  在你俩开始说一些会后悔的话时
please, before you say something you both regret,
我想先点菜
I'd like to place my order.
好的  稍等  谢尔顿
Yeah, just hang on, Sheldon.
你知道咱俩为什么不能做情侣吗
You know why we can't be together?
因为对的永远你  错的永远我
Because you always have to be right.
才不是呢
Oh, that is not true.
这点我认同莱纳德
I got to go with Leonard on this.
他是我认识的人中犯错最多的
He is wrong more than anyone I know.
我刚想起来现在是我的休息时间
You know what? I just realized I'm on a break.
我叫别人过来给你们点单
I'll get someone else.
莱纳德  你要保证等我们下一个女招待过来以后
Leonard, promise me that when our new waitress comes over,
你绝不可以一会儿跟她玩复合
you will not start a complicated on-again,
一会儿跟她玩翻脸的恋情
off-again relationship with her,
因为我现在非常非常饿
because I am very, very hungry.
真是难以置信
Unbelievable.
你想解释一下你在餐厅里的时候
Mind explaining to me why you were being
表现得像个混蛋一样吗
such a jerk at the restaurant?
我那是努力装作咱们没有复合
I was trying to act like we weren't seeing each other.
-这不是咱俩的计划吗  -不是
- That was the plan, right?  - No,
计划是告诉他们  咱们决定只当朋友
the plan was to tell people we decided to stay friends.
你整天那么讨人厌
That's a little hard to do
弄得我也很难演下去
when you're always being such a tool bag.
我用不着站在这听你数落
You know what? I don't have to stand here and take this crap.
你这是去哪呀
The hell do you think you're going?
咱俩现在不就是一吵完架就上床吗
Isn't sex after fighting kind of what we do now?!
好吧  说得没错
Yeah, kind of, yeah.
我们这是干嘛啊
What are we doing?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我每次幻想到咱俩在一起的场面  结局总是很糟
Every scenario I play out for you and me ends badly.
那是因为你总是想得太多
That's because you overthink everything.
莱纳德  你在听我说话吗
Leonard, are you listening to me?
什么  我在听啊
What? Yeah.
这简直就是个灾难
This is a disaster.
我分明订的是
I distinctly ordered
伦纳德・尼莫伊版的史波克纸模
the Leonard Nimoy Mr. Spock cardboard standee.
扎克瑞・昆图站在我的床脚
Why would I feel safer
怎么能让我觉得安全呢
with Zachary Quinto at the foot of my bed?
不知道啊  可是他演《英雄》的时候挺威猛的啊
I don't know, he was pretty badass on Heroes.
也是  那我就给他一次机会吧
You're right, I'll give him a shot.
等一下
Hang on.
佩妮  你今天的晚饭有安排吗
Penny, do you have plans for dinner?
怎么了  你们要去什么好地方吗
Why, you guys going somewhere?
不是  就咱俩单独吃
No, I mean just you and me.
你有认真考虑过才问我的吗
Uh, have you thought this through?
对  而且我认为我们必须去
Yes, and I think we should go anyway.
不行  我还是做不到
No, can't do it.
抱歉  昆图  你还是滚回去吧
Sorry, Quinto, you're going back.
如果你跟莱纳德复合了
If you and Leonard get back together,
就终于有人可以跟我和谢尔顿
Sheldon and I will finally have someone
出去四人约会了
to go on double dates with.
不能跟我和霍华德出去吗
What about me and Howard?
好吧  我们也可以跟你们四人约会
Fine, we can double with you, too.
太没安全感了
So insecure.
你们俩要去哪吃饭
Where are you guys going to eat?
佩妮
Penny?
佩妮  你愿意接受莱纳德作为你的合法丈夫吗
Do you, Penny, take Leonard to be your lawful wedded husband?
我现在说不愿意
Well, it's a little late for me
有点太迟了  对不对
to start saying no, isn't it?
佩妮
Penny.
抱歉  突然想起来我待会要去一下药店
Sorry, just remembered I've got to stop at the drugstore.